准备好了吗  孩子们
Are you ready, kids?
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
我听不见
I can't hear you
好了船长
Aye aye, captain
是谁住在深海的大菠萝里
Who lives in a pineapple under the sea?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
方方黄黄伸缩自如
Absorbent and yellow and porous is he
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
如果四处探险是你的愿望
If nautical nonsense be something you wish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
那就敲敲甲板让大鱼开路
The drop on the deck and flop like a fish
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
准备
Ready
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob SquarePants
脏  话
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
本字幕仅限学习交流
严禁用于商业用途
蟹堡王
好了
Well
开
一天当中最惨的时间又到了
it's the worst time of the day once again
关
关门时间
Closing time
好了
Well
明天早上见  蟹老板
see you in the am, Mr. Krabs
给我站住  海绵宝宝
Hold on there, SpongeBob
把那堆垃圾带出去扔了
Take that pile of filth out with you
蟹老板  不可以这么说章鱼哥
Mr. Krabs, you shouldn't talk about Squidward like that
他说的是这个垃圾  你个白痴
He means this filth, you loon
出去扔垃圾
Taking out the trash
垃圾桶上的字句
Dumpster writing
人民的呼声
The voice of the people
随泡泡上升  随空气下降
Up with bubbles, down with air
力捧泡泡    打倒空气
线虫也是人
Nematodes are people, too
这些线虫可真是
Those nematodes
有句还没写完的
Here's one somebody didn't finish
章鱼哥好臭
章鱼哥闻起来
Squidward smells
真香
Good
这句写的啥
What's this one?
老螃蟹是
Krabs is a
老    螃    蟹    是
你就是用这张臭嘴来亲你妈的吗
Do you kiss your mother with that mouth?
有时候会亲
Well, sometimes
不过
but not
最近没亲
recently
嗨  收垃圾的
Hi, garbage man
嗨  海绵宝宝
Hi, SpongeBob
嗨  派大星
Hi, Patrick
派大星  你知道这几个字什么意思吗
Hey, Patrick, do you know what this word means?
老螃蟹
Krabs
这不是你那个挥汗如雨的红色老板吗
Isn't that the red, sweaty guy you work for?
不是这几个字
Nuh-uh, not that word
老    螃    蟹    是
是这几个字
That word
我应该知道是什么意思了
I think I know what that means
那是用来增强语气的语气词
That's one of those sentence enhancers
增强语气的语气词
Sentence enhancers?
想要讲话花俏就可以用上
You use them when you want to talk fancy
你只要加到你想讲的话里面然后
You just sprinkle it over anything you say and
嘣
wham-o
你讲的话就会变得辛辣起来了
You got yourself a spicy sentence sandwich
懂了
I get it
我来试试看
Let me try
你好  派大星
Hello, Patrick
天气真
Lovely
不错  你说是不是
day we're having, isn't it
是啊没错  海绵宝宝
Why, yes, it is, SpongeBob
今天
This
天气可真
day is particularly
好啊
lovely
说得真
How
对啊  派大星
right you are, Patrick
你说得对  派大星
You're right, Patrick
这辛辣的话讲的我嘴唇都麻了
My lips are tingling
from the spiciness of this conversation
我的也麻了
Mine, too
我一笑就麻了
It tingles when I laugh
蟹堡王
客人们好
Hello, customers
天气真
Nice
不错啊  你们说是不是
day we're having, huh?
他是不是说了
Did he just say?
对  他说了
Aye, he did
派大星  你
Hey, Patrick, how the
好吗
are you?
挺
Pretty
好  海绵宝宝
good, SpongeBob
这可是家餐厅
I thought this was a restaurant
不是嘴臭大会
not a gutter-mouth convention
顾客们请注意
Attention, customers
今日特餐是
Today's special is a
蟹黄堡  配以油腻
Krabby Patty served in a greasy
酱料  肉饼煎至
sauce and grilled to
恰到好处
perfection
也别忘了来点
And, don't forget to ask us to
薯
the
条
fries
我们乐意
It'll be our
效劳
pleasure
嗨  章鱼哥
Hi, Squidward
你
How the
好吗
are you?
天气真
Nice
不错  是不是啊章鱼哥
day, isn't it, Squidward?
真是不明白
I don't understand
那人明明很有才  完全没必要嘴臭的
That guy's talented, he doesn't have to work blue
咱们到更适合家庭的地方去吧
Let's go somewhere more family oriented
我再也不会来这吃东西了
I'm never eating here again
那俩到处嘴臭的臭鱼烂虾
Those foul-mouthed bottom feeders
最大容量
蟹堡王
The Krusty Krab
人都走光了
She's empty
全体成员
All hands on deck
封住大门
Batten the front doors
加固收银机
Brace the cash register
放出快乐食品
Break out the happy snacks
章鱼哥
Squidward
我那些来花钱的漂亮客人都哪去了
Where have all me beautiful paying customers gone?
显然
Apparently
那两个嘴臭兄弟刚学到了个新词
the two barnacle-mouth brothers
just learned a new word
然后海绵宝宝用话筒到处说这个词
and SpongeBob just said it over the intercom
那词是什么
Well, what was it?
他说了啥
What did he say?
他说
He said
那个  他说了
Well, he said
海绵宝宝  还有你朋友
SpongeBob and friend
给我出列
Front and center
我要以你们言语不当为由
Why, I ought to make the two of you
让你们两个粉刷蟹堡王
paint the Krusty Krab for using such language
可是蟹老板
But, Mr. Krabs
我们只是拿那些来加强语气而已
we were only using our sentence enhancers
没错  这样讲话会花俏
Yeah, it's fancy talk
那话一点都不花俏
There ain't nothing fancy about that word
是不是说
You mean?
没错  就是这话
Yes, that one
现在不准说这话了
Now, quit saying that
这可是脏话
It's a bad word
脏话
Bad word?
没错
Yes, siree
那个是11号脏话
That's bad word number 11
其实  你们绝对不能讲的脏话有13个
In fact, there are 13 bad words you should never use
你不是说只有7个吗
Don't you mean there are only seven?
是水手才会只有7个
Not if you're a sailor
13个
好多
That's a lot of
脏话啊
bad words
行了  小子们
Okay, boys
我要你们向我保证
I want you to promise me
你们不会再讲那种话
you'll never use that word again
我们保证
We promise
真高兴蟹老板告诉我们说
I sure am glad Mr. Krabs told us
我们讲的那话是脏话
that word we were using was a bad word
没错  我也高兴
Yeah, me, too
因为我们这样有格调又见多识广的人
because classy sophisticates like us
绝对不应该用粗话来玷污我们的嘴
should not stain our lips with cursing
确实
Yeah, verily
来玩一盘好玩益智的
Now let's play a nice, wholesome game of
鳗梯棋吧
Eels and Escalators
[ 鳗梯棋：改自蛇梯棋 ]
天啊  我最爱玩了
Oh, boy, my favorite
摇出好手气  小蜗还要新鞋子呢
Come on, Gary needs a new pair of shoes
鳗鱼
Eels
太可惜了  海绵宝宝
Too bad, SpongeBob
你得骑鳗鱼了
You got to ride the eel
该死
Darn
轮我了
My turn
万岁
Hooray
扶梯
Escalators
跑上去
Up, up, up
加油
Come on
扶梯
Escalators
又是鳗鱼
Eels again
轮我了
My turn
扶梯
Escalators
鳗鱼
Eels?
扶梯
Es-kee-lators
这可是你最后的机会了  海绵宝宝
Well, this is your last chance, SpongeBob
你输了
要是你又掷出鳗鱼来  你就输了
If you get eels again, you lose
扶梯
Escalators
鳗鱼
Eels
你说了11号脏话
You said number 11
我不是那意思
I didn't mean
你要理解我啊  派大星
You got to understand, Patrick
我本来是要
I was trying
我想说的是
What I meant to say was
某些话就这么顺口而出了
Some things just slip out
你要理解我啊
You got to understand
放心  海绵宝宝
Don't worry, SpongeBob
这我理解
I understand
蟹老板
Mr. Krabs
别去啊  派大星
No, wait, Patrick
派大星  拜托你别告状
Patrick, no, please don't tell
可是你说了
But you said
我要向蟹老板告你的状了
Now I'm going to tell Mr. Krabs on you
那也得等我先说
Not if I tell first
我可以跑得比你快
I can run faster than you
我们蟹堡王再见
See you at the Krusty Krab
冰淇淋
不要啊
Oh, no
蟹堡王
蟹老板蟹老板蟹老板
Mr. Krabs, Mr. Krabs, Mr. Krabs
啥事啥事啥事
What, what, what?
派大星派大星派大星
Patrick, Patrick, Patrick
咋了咋了咋了
Yes, yes, yes?
他说了他说了他说了
He said, he said, he said
有话快说  小子
Out with it, boy
我跟派大星本来在玩鳗梯棋
Me and Patrick were playing Eels and Escalators
他一直升上去
and he was going up-up-up
我就只能骑鳗鱼
and I had to ride the eel
咱俩狂奔
and then we ran
派大星就说出来了某些话
and Patrick said some things
什么样的话
What kind of things?
那个  他说了
Well, he said
快说
Yes?
那个
Well
就是他说了你说的我们不该说的话
Let's just say he said a certain word
that you said he shouldn't say
而这话刚好就是
and this particular word happens to be
你说的我们不该说的13句话中的11号
word number 11 in a list of 13 words
that you said shouldn't be said
对
Right
刚刚那说的是
What was that part about the
谁啊
who now?
蟹老板蟹老板蟹老板
Mr. Krabs, Mr. Krabs, Mr. Krabs
他说了你说的我们不该说的话
He said that word you said we shouldn't say
我现在要松开你们的嘴
Now I'm going to let go of your lips
等松开完
and when I do
我要你们冷静说出你们想跟我说的事
I want you to calmly tell me what youse need to tell me
懂吗
understand?
他说了
He said
我有没有听错
Do my ears deceive me?
你们应该要为此羞耻才对
You two should be ashamed
扔垃圾时间到
Time to take out the trash
你们两个要学点教训
You two need to be taught a lesson
本来还以为我都说清楚了
I thought I made it clear
不准
Never--
就是不准说11号或者任何一号脏话
and I mean
never use number 11 or any of the 13 bad words
你们两个现在在这好好给我等着
Now, the both of youse wait right here
我去去就回
I'll be back
我们会怎么样
What's going to happen to us?
我们可能会被打40大鞭子
We'll probably get 40 lashes
睫 毛
不会吧
Oh, no
对不起  派大星
I'm sorry, Patrick
蟹老板说得对
Mr. Krabs is right
那种话根本没有说出口的必要
There's no need for words like that
我也对不起  海绵宝宝
I'm sorry, too, SpongeBob
我们来发誓  派大星
Let's make a vow, Patrick
从今天起我们一句脏话都不要说
From this day forth
a foul word shall never pass our lips
我们要当好市民
We will be good citizens
跟蟹老板一样的好市民
just like good old Mr. Krabs
同意
Agreed
行了  你们两个嘴臭的
All right, you two foul mouths
为了惩罚你们乱讲脏话
As punishment for fouling the air
污染了蟹堡王的大好气氛
in me restaurant with your foul words
你们要给蟹堡王
you're going to give the Krusty Krab
全粉刷一遍
a fresh coat of paint
从上到下都要
from top to bottom
我
My
的脚
foot
哪个
What
鬼才往马路
genius put a
乱放
rock in a
石头
path
不知道我脚
Can't you see I got a
要踩这吗
foot here
五六七
Five, six, seven
配个
and with a side of
整个就一堆
a heaping helping of
一整船
and a boatload of
九
Nine
横行
crabbing
十三个都齐了  派大星
That's all 13, Patrick
我们要找你妈告状  蟹老板
We're going to tell your mom, Mr. Krabs
求你们不要
No, please
不要跟我妈讲
Not my mommy
等等  求你们不要跟我妈说
Wait, please don't tell me mother
她的小心脏会遭不住的
I don't think her little old heart can take it
蟹妈妈
Mama Krabs
你们好啊
Well, hello there
蟹妈妈  他说了
Mama Krabs, he said
又再说
and then he said
接着说
and he said
接着再说
again and said
再然后他就扯着嗓子大叫
and then he screamed at the top of his voice
然后他
and he
蟹妈妈  他根本不放心上
Mrs. Krabs, he didn't care
简直就是一股
Such a stream of
我从前从来就没有听过这种话
I have never heard in my days
老天爷啊
Oh, dear
我可怜的小心脏
My poor, old heart
亲爱的老妈
Dear mother
那两个嘴臭的对你都干了些什么
What have these foul-mouthed heathens done to you?
你们两个应该感到羞耻
You two should be ashamed
你们居然出口成脏  让个老太太昏倒
Making an old lady faint with your sailor talk
你们都应该感到羞耻
You should all be ashamed
要是你们要像水手那样出口成脏
And if you're going to talk like sailors
那你们就得像水手那样好好干活
then you're going to work like sailors
你们这些小捣蛋可以来领柠檬水了
I guess you scalawags have earned a glass of lemonade
我的
My
脚
foot
老妈
Mother
咋了
What?
声音是老头简金斯跟他那辆破车发的
It's old man Jenkins and his jalopy
蟹太太好
Howdy, Mrs. K
不知名的艺术家
分镜总监
翻译: 1440kHz
分镜
编剧
动画总监
创意总监
翻译: 1440kHz
成人学习中心
我老想有这么一天了
How I have dreamed of this day
章鱼哥先生  艺术教授
Mr. Tentacles, Professor of Art
真是献给裤头村居民们的大好机会
What a marvelous opportunity
for the people of Bikini Bottom
把你们那群没事干的家庭主妇都带来
Bring me your huddled masses of bored housewives
我要把她们塑造成我心中的大好形象
and I will shape them in my image
我会名垂青史
I'll go down in history
终有一天  会有座挂着我名字的展厅
Someday, there will be a wing with my name on it
建在全世界所有博物馆里
in all the museums of the world
兄弟  你这是在活动中心教艺术
Dude, you're teaching art at the rec center
冷静点
Calm down
没文化的垃圾废物
Uncultured trash urchin
九点了
9:00 a.m.
该让同学们进来了
Time to let the class in
可不能再让他们继续等下去了
Well, don't want to keep them waiting any longer
欢迎来上艺术课
Welcome to art class
不是烹饪课吗
Isn't this "Cooking"?
抱歉
Sorry
嗨  章鱼哥
Hi, Squidward
你也是来上这节艺术课的吗
Are you taking this art class, too?
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob?
来上艺术课
In art class
都别走
Wait
这是烹饪课
This is Cooking
快回来
Come back
你肯定是在逗我
You've got to be kidding
太棒了
This is great
我跟你一起来上学
You and me in school together
那老师在哪
So, where's the teacher?
就在你眼前
You're looking at him
你就是老师
You are the "Teacher"
就在我这学生眼前
to my "Pupil"?
这根本不是艺术课
This isn't art class
简直就是天堂
It's heaven
没错
Yeah
带点天堂走  开始上课
Grab a little piece of heaven and let's get on with it
我准备好了  章鱼哥老师
I'm ready, Mr. Tentacles
那你是想当个艺术家吗  海绵宝宝
So, you want to be an artist, eh, SpongeBob?
想
Yes, please
艺术可不全是嬉耍打闹
Well, art is not all fun and games
而是勤奋苦干
It's a lot of hard work
好的
Okay
首先  跟我念
First, repeat after me
我没有才华
I have no talent
章鱼哥老师满腹才华
Mr. Tentacles has all the talent
我有幸的话
If I'm lucky
也许可以沾点章鱼哥老师的才华
some of Mr. Tentacles' talent may rub off on me
我有幸的话
If I'm lucky
才华老师的章鱼触手可以沾我艺术
Mr. Talent will rub his tentacles on my art
随你便
Whatever
好了
Okay
既然你说你先前没练过
Since you're telling me you have no prior training
那就从零开始
we'll have to start from square one
也可以说是
or should I say
从圆开始
circle one
我教得太快了吗  海绵宝宝
Am I going too fast for you, SpongeBob?
这个行不  章鱼哥
How's this, Squidward?
什
What the
怎
How the
完美的圆
A perfect circle?
再画一遍
Do it again
给我看你画的过程
Show your process
那个
Well
首先画出来这个脑袋
First, I draw this head
然后再擦掉一点点细节
Then I erased some of the more detailed features
然后一二三
And one, two, three
画了个圆
a circle
玩意
thingy
快给我
Give me that
别管什么圆了
Forget the circles
不错  章鱼哥
Nice one, Squidward
我来试试看
Let me try
章鱼哥你看
Lookey, Squidward
是我跟你在玩跳山羊
It's you and me playing leapfrog
下面那个是你
That's you on the bottom
快给我
Give me that
跳山羊跟艺术半毛钱关系都没
There is nothing artistic about leapfrog
你这又是在干什么
What are you doing now?
这个叫做  小碎屑
I call it rippy bits
拿一堆碎纸屑来
You take a bunch of old, ripped-up paper
画出来幅画
and make a new picture out of it
看见没
See
这回你在
You're on top
上
this
面
time
你到底还学不学艺术
Do you want to learn art or not?
对不起  章鱼哥
I'm sorry, Squidward--
我会认真听的
I'll listen
好了  海绵宝宝
All right, SpongeBob
给我全神贯注
Pay close attention
看着大理石
Look at your marble
构思出它内在的雕塑的模样
Visualize the sculpture within
再轻轻地
Then gently
这个怎么样  章鱼哥
How's this, Squidward?
好美啊
It's beautiful
我是说
I mean
这根本算不上雕塑
This isn't a sculpture
要雕出好雕塑就要花
A good sculpture takes
更多时间
more time
不能一下子就马上雕好
You can't just sculpt willy-nilly
必须要照着书本上的做
You've got to go by the book
艺术的规矩
照着规矩去做
follow the rules
否则你就不可能越过
Otherwise you'll never get past
这种业余阶段
amateur hour here
并且你鼻子也雕错了
Besides, you got the nose wrong
好了
There
这才叫艺术
Now it's art
这都明摆着了
It's so obvious
我从来没想过得那样
I would have never thought of that
对不起  章鱼哥
I'm sorry, Squidward
我来这学艺术
I came here to learn
却傲慢地顶撞了你的课
and I arrogantly shunned your lessons
我没办法成为像你一样伟大的艺术家
I'll never be a great artist like you
我不配让你来教我
I don't deserve your tutoring
我不配出现在你面前
I don't deserve to be in your presence
我甚至都不配用你的门
I don't even deserve to use your doors
你好啊
Hello, there
我只配这样
But I did deserve that
还有这样
I deserved that, too
我也只配这样
And I deserve this
垃圾场
午安  先生
Good day, sir
不好意思  下课了
Sorry, class is dismissed
你来太迟了
You're too late
真抱歉  我失礼了
I beg your pardon, but I'd forgotten my manners
我叫钱袋蒙蒂
My name is Monty P. Moneybags
世界知名的艺术收藏家
The world-famous art collector?
独一无二
The one and only
你来这有何贵干
Well, what are you doing here?
我在做大采购
I'm on a shopping spree
给我新开的博物馆买艺术品
buying art for my new museum
你不用再去找了
Your search is over
我正是裤头村最伟大的艺术家
I am Bikini Bottom's greatest artiste
这个叫做  章鱼哥的化身
I call this one Squidward in Repose
我
I
觉得这玩意跟我的其他藏品会不搭
don't think that will fit in
with the other pieces in my collection
为什么
Why not?
因为我那都是艺术藏品
Because it's an art collection
这个怎么样
How about this one?
这个叫做  大胆创造
I call it Bold and Brash
应该得叫  垃圾创造
More like Belongs in the Trash
抱歉
Sorry
我肯定是忘了清理掉这份了
I must have missed that one
我怕是得要
Maybe I should be
这是什么
What is that?
先别
Wait, wait
那个不是
That's not
是
It's, uh
天使一样的形体
Angelic form
精妙无比的细节
Amazing detail
恰到好处的和谐
Perfect censorship
这就是天才的杰作
This is the work of a true genius
哎哟
Hello?
这啥玩意
What's this?
这是唯一的缺陷
This is the only flaw
这还差不多
That's more like it
我必须要找到做出这个的艺术家
I simply must find the artist responsible
他会拥有名声
He shall have fame
名声
Fame
财富
Fortune
期望得到的任何东西
Anything his heart desires
任何东西
Anything?
就是我
It's me
我雕出来的
I'm responsible
我能预见到
I can see it now
你名字会挂进全世界最著名的博物馆
Your name in the world's most prestigious museums
我要让你  名垂千古
I am going to make you immortal
现在
Now, uh
帮我把这个抬到车上
help me get this in the car
我需要来人帮个忙
I could use a little help
我的名声
My fame
我的财富
My fortune
我的头发
My hair
这可真是有点倒霉
Well, that's a bit of bad luck right there
不过
But
对你这种伟大的艺术家应当不成问题
this shouldn't be a problem
for an artist of your magnitude
可以马上再雕另外一个
You can whip up another one
没错
Yeah
没问题
No problem
我跟你说  你别传出去
You know, between you and me
我发挥最佳的作品可不是这个
this isn't my best work
要不你明天过来吧
Why don't you come back tomorrow
到时候我保证有东西能让你惊掉袜子
and I'll have something
that will really knock your socks off
我跟你说  我没穿袜子
Between you and me, I'm not wearing socks
没错  没穿袜子
Yeah, no socks
那行  明天见
Okay, see you tomorrow
再见
Bye
我得找到海绵宝宝
I've got to find SpongeBob
垃圾场
海绵宝宝
SpongeBob
你走吧  章鱼哥
Go away, Squidward
我配不上你的一片好心
I don't deserve your kindness
打起精神来
Cheer up
我决定要再给你一次机会
I have decided to give you another chance
有我这样的良师在  一切皆有可能
Why, with a great teacher like me, anything is possible
别看我了  章鱼哥
Don't look at me, Squidward
这都是耻辱
Don't look at my shame
这两只手就不能用来创造
These hands weren't meant to create
只能毁灭
They only destroy
我都没法直视
I can't look at them
没事  海绵宝宝
Come on, SpongeBob
你已经有双可爱的小黄手了
You've got yourself a pair of yellow dandies here
有我帮忙  就会变成创造美的工具
and with my help, we'll turn them into tools of beauty
真的吗
Really?
真的
Really
真的吗
Really?
真的
Really
真的吗
Really?
真的
Really
真的吗
Really?
走吧
Let's go
章鱼哥你看
Squidward, look
是大胆创造
It's old Bold and Brash
快给我
Give me that
好了  海绵宝宝
Okay, SpongeBob
做你之前做过的就行
Just do what you did before
我不行
I can't
等下
Wait, wait
我来帮你一把
Let me help
我们再来从圆开始
Let's start with the circle again
好了  章鱼哥
I did it, Squidward
可是
But, but
脑袋呢
what about the head
还有擦掉
and the erasing
还有
and the, the
我都不知道  章鱼哥
I don't know, Squidward
艺术的规矩
那玩意没写在书上
That stuff's not in the book
那这个呢
How about this, huh?
记不记得
Remember?
这玩意也没写在书上
That's not in the book either
不要管什么书了
Forget about the book
这可真是乱  海绵宝宝
Look at all this mess, SpongeBob
你看到这些小纸片想要做什么
What do all these little bits of paper
make you want to do?
等会  这个我会
Wait, I know this
等会  快成了
Wait, I think I got it
快了快了  好了
There you go and yes
好  海绵宝宝
Okay, SpongeBob
直接来弄大理石吧
Let's just move on to the marble
艺术家首先要专心构思作品
First, an artist must concentrate
and visualize his concept
这就对了
Now you've got it
我得抱大理石
I've got to embrace the marble
对
Right
我得闻大理石
I've got to sniff the marble
那个
Well, uh
好
okay
我得舔大理石
I've got to lick the marble
我得洗大理石
I've got to wash the marble
我得约大理石
I've got to date the marble
我得变大理石
I've got to be the marble
成了
I've got it
我看到大理石内在的雕塑了
I have seen the sculpture within
给你  老弟
Here you go, Buddy
有了这工具  我就要诞生出艺术了
With this tool, I shall give birth to art
老天爷啊
Oh, boy
还有一样东西
But one more thing
好了
There
现在这是艺术了
Now it's art
你觉得怎么样  章鱼哥
Well, what do you think, Squidward?
尽心欣赏一小会
Just take it all in for a moment
沉浸其中吧
Let it soak in
好像我的艺术成就
It looks like the excitement of my artistic triumph
让章鱼哥兴奋过头了
is too much for Squidward
行吧  回垃圾场
Oh, well, back to the dump
垃圾场  垃圾场
To the dump, to the dump
垃圾场场场
To the dump, dump, dump
垃圾场  垃圾场
To the dump, to the dump
垃圾场场场
To the dump, dump, dump
我是来这
I'm here for the
什么
What the
这都是谁干的
Who is responsible for this?
现在这些全是他干的
As of now, it's his responsibility
再见  先生
Good day to you, sir
你就是史上最伟大的艺术家
You, sir, are the greatest artist who ever lived